pwnthis.net 2018-02-27

# Disclaimer @ PWNTHIS

#### LIKE if you want more awesome cheats!

All information provided in **PWNTHIS.NET** is provided for information purposes only and does not constitute a legal contract between **PWNTHIS.NET** and any person or entity unless otherwise specified.   
Information presented on this website may be distributed or copied. All rights reserved. The use of the articles is allowed only when quoting the source - PWNTHIS.NET, having web addresses at www.pwnthis.net.

Some of the publications on this server may contain live references (or pointers) to information created and maintained by other organisations. Please note that **PWNTHIS.NET** does not control, monitor or guarantee the information contained in these publications or information contained in links to other external web sites, and does not endorse any views expressed or products or services offered therein. In no event shall **PWNTHIS.NET** be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any such content, goods, or services available on or through any such publication or resource. 

The information posted does not neccessarily represent the official opinion of PWNTHIS.   
PWNTHIS welcomes suggestions on how to improve our web-site and correct errors. 

**Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is important to PWNTHIS. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that PWNTHIS collects, and the ways in which PWNTHIS uses that personal information.

Personal information collection

PWNTHIS may collect and use the following kinds of personal information: 

 [information about your use of this website (including Name, Email address);]   
 [information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including Email Address);]

 [information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including Email); and]  
 [any other information that you send to PWNTHIS.]

Using personal information

PWNTHIS may use your personal information to: 

 [administer this website;]  
 [personalize the website for you;]  
 [enable your access to and use of the website services;]  
 [publish information about you on the website;]  
 [send to you products that you purchase;]  
 [supply to you services that you purchase;]  
 [send you statements and invoices;]  
 [collect payments from you; and]  
 [send you marketing communications.]

Where PWNTHIS discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement. 

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, PWNTHIS may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Securing your data

PWNTHIS will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. 

PWNTHIS will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers. 

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be protected by encryption technology.]

Updating this statement

PWNTHIS may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website. 

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes. 

Other websites

This website contains links to other websites. 

PWNTHIS is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Contact PWNTHIS

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or PWNTHIS treatment of your personal information, please write to:

 by email to pwnthis.net@gmail.com; or 

Also, rest assured that no information is retrieved from users and we will protect your privacy. 

 \----------------------------
